English --------------------------- BitDozer - the first remote Bitcoin client for Windows Phone!  With BitDozer, you can connect to a Bitcoin daemon (not included) that is running and accessible on the internet using the username and password as configured at the server.  Once connected to your Bitcoin server, you can then:  - View the contents of your wallet including accounts, addresses, transactions,   - Send bitcoins from the server's wallet to another bitcoin address,  - Send a request for bitcoin payment to another device via SMS  - Monitor the server status  French --------------------------- BitDozer - le client Bitcoin première télécommande pour Windows Phone!   Avec BitDozer, vous pouvez vous connecter à un démon de Bitcoin (non inclus) qui est en marche et accessible sur Internet en utilisant le nom d'utilisateur et mot de passe tel qu'il est configuré au niveau du serveur.   Une fois connecté à votre serveur Bitcoin, vous pouvez alors:   - Afficher le contenu de votre portefeuille, y compris les comptes, les adresses, les transactions,   - Envoyer bitcoins de portefeuille du serveur vers une autre adresse Bitcoin,   - Envoyer une demande de paiement Bitcoin à un autre appareil via SMS   - Surveiller l'état du serveur  Italian --------------------------- BitDozer - il primo client Bitcoin remoto per Windows Phone!   Con BitDozer, è possibile connettersi a un demone Bitcoin (non incluso) che è in esecuzione e accessibile su Internet utilizzando il nome utente e la password come configurato sul server.   Una volta connesso al server Bitcoin, è possibile:   - Visualizza il contenuto del tuo portafogli compresi i conti, gli indirizzi, le transazioni,   - Invia bitcoins dal portafoglio del server ad un altro indirizzo bitcoin,   - Invia una richiesta di pagamento bitcoin ad un altro dispositivo via SMS   - Monitorare lo stato del server  Spanish --------------------------- BitDozer - el primer cliente Bitcoin a distancia para Windows Phone!   Con BitDozer, se puede conectar a un demonio Bitcoin (no incluido) que se está ejecutando y accesible en el Internet utilizando el nombre de usuario y contraseña tal como está configurado en el servidor.   Una vez conectado a su servidor Bitcoin, a continuación, puede:   - Ver el contenido de su cartera, incluyendo las cuentas, direcciones, las transacciones,   - Enviar Bitcoin de la billetera del servidor a otra dirección bitcoin,   - Enviar una solicitud de pago bitcoin a otro dispositivo a través de SMS   - Supervisar el estado del servidor  Portugese --------------------------- BitDozer - o cliente Bitcoin primeiro remoto para Windows Phone!   Com BitDozer, você pode se conectar a um daemon Bitcoin (não incluído), que está em execução e acessível na internet usando o nome de usuário e senha configurados no servidor.   Uma vez conectado ao seu servidor Bitcoin, então você pode:   - Exibir o conteúdo de sua carteira, incluindo contas, endereços, transações,   - Enviar bitcoins da carteira do servidor para outro endereço bitcoin,   - Enviar um pedido de pagamento bitcoin a outro dispositivo via SMS   - Monitorar o status do servidor  Arabic --------------------------- BitDozer - أول عميل Bitcoin بعيد عن هاتف ويندوز!   مع BitDozer، يمكنك الاتصال إلى شيطان Bitcoin (غير المدرجة) الذي يقوم بتشغيل ويمكن الوصول إليها على شبكة الإنترنت باستخدام اسم المستخدم وكلمة السر كما في تكوين الخادم.   مرة واحدة متصلة إلى الخادم Bitcoin الخاص بك، يمكنك بعد ذلك:   - عرض محتويات محفظتك بما في ذلك الحسابات، وعناوين، والمعاملات،   - إرسال bitcoins من المحفظة للملقم إلى عنوان آخر bitcoin،   - إرسال طلب لدفع bitcoin إلى جهاز آخر عبر الرسائل القصيرة   - متابعة حالة الخادم  German --------------------------- BitDozer - die erste Remote-Bitcoin-Client für Windows Phone!   Mit BitDozer, können Sie zu einem Bitcoin Daemon (nicht enthalten), die ausgeführt wird, und über das Internet zugänglich mit dem Benutzernamen und Passwort wie auf dem Server konfiguriert verbinden.   Nachdem es mit dem Bitcoin Server verbunden sind, können Sie dann:   - Zeigen Sie den Inhalt Ihrer Brieftasche einschließlich Konten, Adressen, Transaktionen,   - Senden Sie Bitcoins aus der Server-Brieftasche zu einem anderen Bitcoin-Adresse,   - Senden Sie eine Anfrage für Bitcoin Zahlung auf ein anderes Gerät per SMS   - Überwachen Sie den Server-Status  Russian --------------------------- BitDozer - первый удаленный клиент Bitcoin для телефонов Windows!   С BitDozer, вы можете подключиться к Bitcoin демон (не входит), который работает и доступен в Интернете, используя имя пользователя и пароль в соответствии с настройками на сервере.   После подключения к серверу Bitcoin, вы можете:   - Просмотр содержимого вашего бумажника в том числе счета, адреса, операции,   - Отправить bitcoins из бумажника сервера на другой адрес Bitcoin,   - Запрос на Bitcoin оплаты к другому устройству с помощью SMS   - Мониторинг состояния сервера  Polish --------------------------- BitDozer - pierwszy klient zdalnego Bitcoin dla Windows Phone!   Z BitDozer, można podłączyć do Bitcoin demon (brak w zestawie), na którym działa i dostępnym w Internecie za pomocą loginu i hasła jak skonfigurować na serwerze.   Po podłączeniu do serwera Bitcoin, możesz:   - Zobacz zawartość swojego portfela, w tym kont, adresy, transakcji,   - Wyślij bitcoins z serwera portfela na inny adres bitcoin,   - Wyślij wniosek o płatność bitcoin do innego urządzenia za pomocą wiadomości SMS   - Monitorowanie stanu serwera  Romanian --------------------------- BitDozer - primul client Bitcoin de la distanţă pentru Windows Phone!   Cu BitDozer, vă puteţi conecta la un demon Bitcoin (nu sunt incluse), care se rulează şi accesibil pe internet, folosind numele de utilizator şi parola configurat de la server.   Odata conectat la serverul de Bitcoin dumneavoastră, puteţi apoi:   - Vezi conţinutul portofelului dvs., inclusiv conturi, adrese, tranzactii,   - Trimite bitcoins din portofel serverul de la o altă adresă bitcoin,   - Trimite o cerere de plată bitcoin la un alt dispozitiv prin SMS   - Monitorizarea Server Status  Chinese (Simplified) ---------------------------- BitDozer - 为Windows Phone的第一个远程Bitcoin客户端！  随着BitDozer，你可以连接到1的Bitcoin守护（不含税），正在运行，并且对互联网的使用在服务器上配置的用户名和密码访问。  一旦连接到你的Bitcoin服务器，然后你可以：   - 查看帐户，地址，交易的内容，包括你的钱包，   - 服务器的钱包从另一个bitcoin地址发送bitcoins   - 发送bitcoin通过短信支付到另一台设备的要求   - 监控服务器的状态  Chinese (Traditional) --------------------------- BitDozer - 為Windows Phone的第一個遠程Bitcoin客戶端！  隨著BitDozer，你可以連接到1的Bitcoin守護（不含稅），正在運行，並且對互聯網的使用在服務器上配置的用戶名和密碼訪問。  一旦連接到你的Bitcoin服務器，然後你可以：   - 查看帳戶，地址，交易的內容，包括你的錢包，   - 服務器的錢包從另一個bitcoin地址發送bitcoins   - 發送bitcoin通過短信支付到另一台設備的要求   - 監控服務器的狀態  Czech --------------------------- BitDozer - první dálkový Bitcoin klient pro Windows Phone!   S BitDozer, můžete se připojit k Bitcoin démon (není součástí dodávky), který je spuštěn a přístupné na internetu pomocí uživatelského jména a hesla, jak nastavit na serveru.   Po připojení k serveru Bitcoin, pak můžete:   - Podívejte se na obsah vaší peněženky, včetně účetnictví, adresy, transakcích,   - Poslat bitcoins ze serveru peněženky na jinou adresu bitcoin,   - Zaslat žádost o platbu bitcoin na jiné zařízení přes SMS   - Sledování stavu serveru  Danish -------------------------- BitDozer - den første fjernbetjening Bitcoin klient til Windows Phone!   Med BitDozer, kan du oprette forbindelse til en Bitcoin dæmon (ikke inkluderet), der kører og tilgængelig på internettet ved hjælp af brugernavn og adgangskode som konfigureret på serveren.   Når tilsluttet din Bitcoin server, kan du:   - Se indholdet af din tegnebog herunder regnskaber, adresser, transaktioner,   - Send bitcoins fra serverens tegnebog til en anden bitcoin adresse,   - Send en anmodning om bitcoin betaling til en anden enhed via SMS   - Overvågning af server status  Dutch -------------------------- BitDozer - de eerste op afstand Bitcoin client voor Windows Phone!   Met BitDozer, kunt u verbinding maken met een Bitcoin daemon (niet inbegrepen) die wordt uitgevoerd en toegankelijk op het internet met behulp van de gebruikersnaam en het wachtwoord zoals geconfigureerd op de server.   Eenmaal verbonden aan het Bitcoin server, kunt u dan:   - Bekijk de inhoud van je portemonnee inclusief rekeningen, adressen, transacties,   - Bitcoins Stuur van de server de portemonnee van een ander Bitcoin adres,   - Stuur een verzoek om Bitcoin betaling aan een ander apparaat via SMS   - Controleer de server status  Filipino -------------------------- BitDozer - ang unang remote Bitcoin na client para sa Windows Phone!  Sa BitDozer, maaari mong kumonekta sa isang Bitcoin demonyo (hindi kasama) na ay tumatakbo at access sa internet gamit ang username at password na na-configure sa server.  Kapag konektado sa ang iyong Bitcoin server, maaari mong:  - Tingnan ang mga nilalaman ng iyong wallet kasama ang mga account, address, transaksyon,  - Magpadala ng mga bitcoins mula sa wallet ng server sa ibang address bitcoin,  - Magpadala ng isang kahilingan para sa bitcoin pagbabayad sa ibang aparato sa pamamagitan ng SMS  - Subaybayan ang server status  Finnish -------------------------- BitDozer - ensimmäinen kauko Bitcoin asiakas Windows Phone!   Kun BitDozer, voit muodostaa yhteyden Bitcoin daemon (ei mukana), joka on käynnissä ja saatavilla internetissä käyttäjätunnuksella ja salasanalla kuin määritetty palvelimessa.   Kun kytketty Bitcoin palvelimelle, voit:   - Katso sisällön lompakon kuten tilit, osoitteita, transaktiot,   - Lähetä bitcoins palvelimelta lompakko toiseen bitcoin osoitteeseen,   - Lähetä pyyntö bitcoin maksamista toiseen laitteeseen tekstiviestillä   - Valvo palvelimen tila  Greek -------------------------- BitDozer - το πρώτο remote client Bitcoin για Windows Phone!   Με BitDozer, μπορείτε να συνδεθείτε σε ένα Bitcoin δαίμονα (δεν περιλαμβάνεται) που λειτουργεί και πρόσβαση στο διαδίκτυο χρησιμοποιώντας το όνομα χρήστη και τον κωδικό πρόσβασης, όπως διαμορφώθηκε στο διακομιστή.   Μόλις συνδεθεί με το διακομιστή Bitcoin σας, τότε μπορείτε να:   - Δείτε τα περιεχόμενα του πορτοφολιού σας, συμπεριλαμβανομένων των λογαριασμών, διευθύνσεις, τις συναλλαγές,   - Αποστολή bitcoins από το πορτοφόλι του server σε άλλη διεύθυνση bitcoin,   - Αποστολή ενός αιτήματος για την καταβολή bitcoin σε άλλη συσκευή μέσω SMS   - Την παρακολούθηση της κατάστασης του διακομιστή  Hebrew -------------------------- BitDozer - הלקוח הראשון Bitcoin מרחוק עבור טלפון Windows! עם BitDozer, אתה יכול להתחבר daemon Bitcoin (לא כלול) שבו פועל ונגיש באינטרנט באמצעות  שם המשתמש והסיסמה כפי מוגדר על השרת. לאחר ההתחברות לשרת Bitcoin שלך, אז אתה יכול:   - הצג את תוכן הארנק שלך, כולל חשבונות, כתובות, עסקאות,   - שלח bitcoins מהארנק של השרת לכתובת אחרת bitcoin,   - שלח בקשה לתשלום bitcoin למכשיר אחר באמצעות SMS   - לפקח על מצב השרת  Hindi -------------------------- BitDozer - पहले विंडोज फोन के लिए दूरदराज के Bitcoin ग्राहक!  BitDozer साथ, आप एक Bitcoin (शामिल नहीं) डेमॉन चल रहा है कि उपयोगकर्ता नाम और पासवर्ड का उपयोग कर सर्वर पर विन्यस्त रूप में इंटरनेट पर सुलभ करने के लिए कनेक्ट कर सकते हैं.  एक बार अपने Bitcoin सर्वर से जुड़ा हुआ है, तो आप कर सकते हैं:  खातों, पते, लेनदेन सहित अपने बटुए की सामग्री देखें,  सर्वर का बटुआ से अन्य bitcoin के पते पर bitcoins भेजें  एसएमएस के जरिए bitcoin अन्य डिवाइस के लिए भुगतान के लिए एक अनुरोध भेजें  - मॉनिटर सर्वर स्थिति  Hungarian -------------------------- BitDozer - az első távoli Bitcoin kliens Windows Phone!   A BitDozer, tud-e csatlakozni egy Bitcoin démon (nem tartozék) fut, és hozzáférhető az internet segítségével a felhasználónevet és a jelszót beállítva a szerveren.   Miután csatlakoztatta a Bitcoin szerver, akkor majd:   - Megtekintése az Ön pénztárcáját, beleértve számlák, címek, tranzakciók,   - Küldje bitcoins a szerver egy másik tárcát bitcoin címét,   - Kérelmezheti egy másik bitcoin fizetési eszközzel SMS-ben   - Figyelemmel kíséri a szerver állapotát  Icelandic ------------------------- BitDozer - fyrsta fjarlægur Bitcoin viðskiptavinur fyrir Gluggakista Sími!   Með BitDozer, getur þú tengst við Bitcoin púkinn (ekki innifalinn) sem er í gangi og aðgengilegur á netinu með notendanafn og lykilorð sem stillt á þjóninum.   Einu sinni tengdur til Bitcoin miðlara, getur þú þá:   - Skoða innihald veskinu þ.mt bókhaldi, heimilisföng, viðskipti,   - Senda bitcoins úr veskinu miðlara til annars bitcoin heimilisfang,   - Senda beiðni um bitcoin greiðslu til annað tæki í gegnum SMS   - Fylgst með miðlara stöðu  Indonesian ------------------------- BitDozer - klien Bitcoin pertama remote untuk Windows Phone!   Dengan BitDozer, Anda dapat terhubung ke daemon Bitcoin (tidak termasuk) yang berjalan dan dapat diakses di internet dengan menggunakan username dan password sebagai dikonfigurasi pada server.   Setelah terhubung ke server Bitcoin Anda, maka Anda dapat:   - Melihat isi dompet Anda termasuk rekening, alamat, transaksi,   - Kirim bitcoins dari dompet server ke alamat bitcoin,   - Mengirim permintaan untuk pembayaran bitcoin ke perangkat lain melalui SMS   - Memantau status server  Japanese ---------------------- BitDozer - Windowsの携帯電話の最初のリモートBitcoinクライアント！  BitDozerを使用すると、Bitcoin実行されているデーモン（​​含まれていません）とサーバで構成されたユーザー名とパスワードを使用してインターネット上でアクセス可能に接続することができます。  一度して、あなたのBitcoinサーバにすることができます接続：   - アカウント、アドレス、トランザクションを含むウォレットの内容を表示し、   - サーバーの財布から別のbitcoinアドレスにbitcoinsを送信すると、   - SMSを介して別のデバイスへのbitcoinの支払いのために要求を送信   - サーバのステータスを監視  Norwegian ------------------------- BitDozer - den første eksterne Bitcoin klient for Windows Phone!   Med BitDozer, kan du koble til en Bitcoin daemon (ikke inkludert) som kjører og tilgjengelig på internett ved hjelp av brukernavn og passord som konfigurert på serveren.   Når du er koblet til din Bitcoin server, kan du:   - Vis innholdet av lommeboken din, inkludert regnskap, adresser, transaksjoner,   - Send bitcoins fra serveren lommebok til en annen bitcoin adresse,   - Send en forespørsel for bitcoin betaling til en annen enhet via SMS   - Overvåk server status  Persian ----------------------------- BitDozer - اولین مشتری Bitcoin از راه دور برای گوشی ویندوز!  با BitDozer، شما می توانید به یک شبح Bitcoin (شامل نمی شود) که در حال اجرا است و بر روی اینترنت با استفاده از نام کاربری و رمز عبور را در سرور پیکربندی شده در دسترس ارتباط برقرار کنند.  یک بار به سرور Bitcoin شما متصل شده، بعد از آن شما می توانید:  - مشاهده محتویات کیف پول خود را از جمله حساب ها، آدرس ها، معاملات،  - ارسال bitcoins ها از کیف پول سرور را به آدرس دیگری bitcoin،  - ارسال درخواست برای پرداخت bitcoin به دستگاه دیگر از طریق SMS  - نظارت بر وضعیت سرور  Slovak ---------------------------- BitDozer - prvý diaľkový Bitcoin klient pre Windows Phone!   S BitDozer, môžete sa pripojiť k Bitcoin démon (nie je súčasťou dodávky), ktorý je spustený a prístupné na internete pomocou užívateľského mena a hesla, ako nastaviť na serveri.   Po pripojení k serveru Bitcoin, potom môžete:   - Pozrite sa na obsah vašej peňaženky, vrátane účtovníctva, adresy, transakciách,   - Poslať bitcoins zo servera peňaženky na inú adresu bitcoin,   - Zaslať žiadosť o platbu bitcoin na iné zariadenia cez SMS   - Sledovanie stavu servera  Slovenian -------------------------- BitDozer - prvi daljinski Bitcoin odjemalec za Windows Phone!   Z BitDozer lahko povežete z Bitcoin daemon (ni priložen), ki se izvaja in je dostopna na internetu s pomočjo uporabniškega imena in gesla, kot je nastavljen na strežniku.   Ko je priključen na Bitcoin strežniku, lahko potem:   - Oglejte si vsebino vaše denarnice, vključno z računi, naslovi, transakcije,   - Pošljite bitcoins iz denarnice strežnika na drug naslov bitcoin,   - Pošlje zahtevek za izplačilo bitcoin v drugo napravo preko SMS   - Spremljati stanje strežnika  Swedish -------------------------- BitDozer - den första fjärrkontrollen Bitcoin klient för Windows Phone!   Med BitDozer, kan du ansluta till en Bitcoin demon (medföljer ej) som körs och tillgänglig på Internet med hjälp av användarnamn och lösenord som konfigureras på servern.   När du är ansluten till din Bitcoin servern kan du sedan:   - Visa innehållet i din plånbok, inklusive konton, adresser, transaktioner,   - Skicka bitcoins från servern plånbok till en annan Bitcoin adress,   - Skicka en begäran om Bitcoin betalning till en annan enhet via SMS   - Övervaka serverns status  Thai -------------------------- BitDozer - ไคลเอนต์ Bitcoin แรกระยะไกลสำหรับ Windows โทรศัพท์!   ด้วย BitDozer คุณสามารถเชื่อมต่อกับภูต Bitcoin (ไม่รวม) ที่กำลังเรียกใช้และสามารถเข้าถึงได้บนอินเทอร์เน็ตโดยใช้ชื่อผู้ใช้และรหัสผ่านเป็นค่าที่เซิร์ฟเวอร์   เมื่อเชื่อมต่อไปยังเซิร์ฟเวอร์ Bitcoin ของคุณคุณสามารถแล้ว:   - ดูเนื้อหาของกระเป๋าสตางค์ของคุณรวมถึงบัญชี, ที่อยู่, รายการ,   - ส่ง bitcoins จากกระเป๋าสตางค์ของเซิร์ฟเวอร์ไปยังอีกที่อยู่ bitcoin,   - ส่งคำขอสำหรับการชำระเงิน bitcoin ไปยังอุปกรณ์อื่นผ่านทาง SMS   - ตรวจสอบสถานะเซิร์ฟเวอร์  Turkish -------------------------- BitDozer - Windows Phone için ilk uzaktan Bitcoin müşteri!   BitDozer ile, bir Bitcoin çalışan daemon (dahil değil) ve sunucuda yapılandırılmış olarak kullanıcı adı ve şifreyi kullanarak internet üzerinden erişilebilir bağlanabilirsiniz.   Bir kere, sonra Bitcoin sunucuya bağlandığı:   - Hesapları, adresleri, işlemleri de dahil olmak üzere cüzdan içeriğini görüntüle   - Sunucunun cüzdanından başka bir bitcoin adrese bitcoins gönder   - SMS üzerinden başka bir cihaza bitcoin ödeme talebi gönderin   - Sunucu durumunu izleme  Ukranian -------------------------- BitDozer - перший віддалений клієнт Bitcoin для телефонів Windows!   З BitDozer, ви можете підключитися до Bitcoin демон (не входить), який працює і доступний в Інтернеті, використовуючи ім'я користувача і пароль відповідно до настройками на сервері.   Після підключення до сервера Bitcoin, ви можете:   - Перегляд вмісту вашого гаманця в тому числі рахунки, адреси, операції,   - Відправити bitcoins з гаманця сервера на іншу адресу Bitcoin,   - Запит на Bitcoin оплати до іншого пристрою за допомогою SMS   - Моніторинг стану сервера  Vietnamese -------------------------- BitDozer - Bitcoin khách hàng từ xa đầu tiên cho Windows Phone!  Với BitDozer, bạn có thể kết nối với một daemon Bitcoin (không bao gồm) đang chạy và truy cập trên internet bằng cách sử dụng tên người dùng và mật khẩu cấu hình máy chủ.  Sau khi kết nối với máy chủ Bitcoin của bạn, bạn có thể sau đó:  - Xem nội dung chi tiêu của bạn bao gồm tài khoản, địa chỉ, giao dịch,  - Gửi bitcoins cho từ ví tiền của máy chủ đến một địa chỉ bitcoin,  - Gửi yêu cầu cho bitcoin thanh toán cho một thiết bị khác qua tin nhắn SMS  - Theo dõi tình trạng máy chủ                           